whatscheaper.com 2012-11-07

# Whatscheaper.com - Privacy Policy

PRIVACY

**WHATSCHEAPER.COM has the following Privacy policy. Please read it in its entirety!**

Your privacy is very important to us ("we" or "us"). This privacy policy ("policy") describes the practices that apply to our site ("site"), including, specifically, the information we collect about you, when and how we collect that information and what may happen to that information. 

**Simply put:**   
We will not collect personally identifiable information like your name, e-mail and mailing address and telephone number ("Personal Information") without your knowledge and permission. We will not disclose your Personal Information to third parties unless you have authorized us to do so. 

We will take reasonable steps to protect the security of the Personal Information we collect from you. The remainder of this policy describes our information handling practices in detail. 

**When You Are Just Visiting Us:** **  
** You can always visit our site without revealing who you are or providing any Personal Information. We do collect usage information ("session data"), but it is anonymous and is not linked to you as an individual. We use session data to better understand things like how our site is navigated, how many visitors arrive at specific pages, the length and frequency of stays at our site, the variety of searches of our sites database, the types of browsers and computer operating systems used by our visitors and the Internet Protocol addresses from which our visitors connect to our site. We use this information to improve our site content and ease of use.

**If you decide To fill out one of our subscription or contact forms:**  

  * **_a) Personal Information_**   
 If you decide to fill out one of our subscription or contact forms, we will collect Personal Information about you that you voluntarily share with us. We collect Personal Information that is necessary for us to provide you with the services offered on our site. As mentioned, this Personal Information includes things like your name, e-mail and mailing address and telephone number. 
  * **_b) Sharing of Personal Information_**   
 Other than as explained in this policy, we will not disclose any Personal Information we collect from you to others without your permission, except in certain limited circumstances: 
    1. to protect the security of our site and our rights under our Terms and Conditions of Use; 
    2. to protect ourselves against liability; 
    3. in response to legal process, 
    4. if we believe in good faith that the law requires it; or 
    5. in connection with a sale of our business or company. 
  * **_c) Additional Products and Services_**   
 We may partner with other companies to offer you additional products or services. If you sign up for any of these additional products or services, such as (but not limited too) "Fare Alerts" (which cover Flight, Car, and Hotels fare notices) we will share your name and any other Personal Information that is necessary for these other companies to provide the products or services you have signed up for. This policy will not cover the use of your Personal Information by these other companies. We encourage you to read each other company privacy policy before signing up for any of these services. 

**Email Addresses, and Subscriptions:**   
When you subscribe to a farealert using the subscription form, we will share your email address with one of our travel partners, but with nobody else. You can unsubscribe at anytime by using our unsubscribe link found in the same area in which you subscribed (on our subscription page). 

**Use of Cookies:**   
To enable features at the Site, we use cookies to collect and maintain aggregated data (such as the number of visitors) to help us see which areas are most popular with our users and improve and update the content on our site. While in the process of browsing our site, you also provide us with information that doesn’t reveal your personal identity what type of destination you’re exploring, for example. We use this aggregated data only as explained in this Privacy Policy. We do not connect aggregated data to any name, address, or other identifying information.   
You may occasionally receive cookies from unaffiliated companies or organizations, to the extent they place advertising on our Site or are linked to the Site. These third-party cookies may collect information about you when you "click" on their advertising or content or link. This practice is standard in the Internet industry. Because of the way in which the Internet operates, we cannot control collection of this information by these third parties, and these cookies are not subject to this Privacy Policy.  

**Links:**   
Our site provides links to other sites. When you click on one of these links, you are leaving our site and entering another site that we do not control and for which we cannot be responsible. You should carefully review the privacy statements or policies on any other site that you visit because those privacy statements or policies will apply to your visit to that site and may be very different from our policy. 

**Google and the DoubleClick Dart cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Your Consent to this Privacy Policy:**   
Use of the Site signifies your consent, as well as the consent of the company for whom you use the Site and whose information you submit (if any), to this on-line Privacy Policy, including the collection and use of information by us, as described in this statement, and also signifies agreement to the terms of use for the Site. Continued access and use of the Site without acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy relieves us from responsibility to the user. 

**We Right To change this Policy:**   
We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any of other policies or practice, at any time and will notify users of such changes or updates by posting them on the Site and/or by additional means as determined to be appropriate under the circumstances. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to the Site. 

HOME
